Gousopoulos Konstantinos

Grigoriou E 21, Larissa 41222, Greece (+30) 6988345682 kgousopoulos@gmail.com www.gousopoulos.gr

Profile

I'm a Software & Android Developer with 2 years of experience in Web Development. I am an undergraduate in the Master of Science (MSc) program "Software Engineering for Internet and Mobile Applications" and I have a degree from Computer Science and Telecommunications department of the Technological Educational Institute (TEI) of Larissa (Greece).

Skills

Programming

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, BootStrap framework, UIKit framework, PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Java, Android, Jade, C, MPI & OpenMP Parallel Programming, Ontological Engineering, RESTful Web Services, UML, Cloud Computing, Data mining

Other

Wordpress, Joomla, Photoshop, Git, PhpStorm, Android Studio, IntelliJ IDEA, Brackets, Linux (Ubuntu), Protégé, RapidMiner, Google App Engine

Experience

Readmore Creative, Larissa (Greece)

Apr 2016 - Nov 2016

Web Developer

As a member of Readmore's team my responsibilities were:

- The designing and development of WebSites
- The designing and development of e-shops
- Technical and Customer Support

FreeLancer

Nov 2015 – Apr 2016

Web Developer

Some of my project as a Freelancer were:

- Designing, development and SEO of the Website gyradikopanoigyroi.gr
- Designing, development and SEO of the Website xenonas-ios.gr

ItBiz Digital Agency, Larissa (Greece)

Web Developer - Promoter

As a member of ItBiz's Digital Agency team my responsibilities were:

- The designing, development and SEO of Websites
- The designing, development and SEO of e-shops
- Technical and Customer Support
- Administrator and promoter of the Website <u>deliverylarissa.gr</u>

Education

Master of Science (MSc)

Graduation on August 2017

Jan 2013 – Sept 2013

Software Engineering for Internet & Mobile Applications Technological Educational Institute (TEI) of Larissa, Greece

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Dec 2014

Computer Science & Telecommunications

Technological Educational Institute (TEI) of Larissa, Greece

Certifications

Oracle Academy

Database Design and Programming with SQL

Android App Development Essential Training

Lynda.com

Certificate No: B6ED58314B6D426780FAEB653A9B0B7

Java Essential Training

Lynda.com

Certificate No: D18321BCE3DB4643A31896AF0D74781A

Connecting Android Apps to RESTful Web Services

Lunda.com

Certificate No: 7456EEDF9E59492B829EB819535C41A8

Other

Languages

Greek(native), English

Hobbies

Reading, Travelling, Music, Guitar, Sports